<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on neoxone.com</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on neoxone.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>12 basic tips for R Code in production</title>
      <link>/2021/09/28/r-basic-tips-for-production-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/09/28/r-basic-tips-for-production-code/</guid>
      <description>h3 { margin-left: -24px; }Disclaimer : No need to follow all the rules, tips and tricks you read.
You are still the best judge when it comes to writing code. Context is a huge factor and you should not rely on any particular advice. Start by writing something that works. It does not need to be perfect.
1. Microbench for performance critical code.Every decision is a trade off in production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumber v1.0 Showcase (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/2021/01/31/plumber-v1-0-showcase-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/01/31/plumber-v1-0-showcase-part-1/</guid>
      <description>When I discovered plumber, I fell in love with its versatility. With version 1.0, it is even more versatile and modular than before. Since I had the chance to contribute to the project, I wanted to share some of the new features that made it into this release.
Part 1New annotation @plumberNew tags were introduced in 1.0. @plumber allows users to interact with the router object during its creation process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying R REST API in production</title>
      <link>/2020/12/12/deploying-r-api-in-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/12/deploying-r-api-in-production/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2018, I had to deploy an R API on kubernetes. It lead to a quick presentation at R à Québec 2019 which is still available here. Since then, I deployed half a dozen more solutions while refining the deployment pipeline. In my opinion, R is a vary viable solution as the stack stays the same through the whole data science cycle. This is more or less the workflow I use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
